digitalfaq.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy – The Digital FAQ

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, partake in our professional services, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience; your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website; we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To send periodic emails; to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, simply unsubscribe via the forum UserCP.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We do not collect credit information, and use third-party payment processors (i.e., Paypal) as needed. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow, that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties the personally identifiable information of legitimate site members. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety; for example, to fight spam with services such as StopForumSpam.com.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Third-party advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies which serve ads and may collect information about site visitors. These companies collect and use the information to provide relevant advertisements on our site, or other sites and mobile apps on the ad network, using cookies or pixels. It’s used to provide info on goods and services that you may find of interest, or to understand user interaction with the ads. For more information, or to opt out of collection, visit the ad network [site](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
